<resources>
    <!-- Categories names -->
    <string name="current_times">Current times tips</string>
    <string name="you_self">Get you self tips</string>
    <string name="family">Family tips</string>
    <string name="relationship">Relationship tips</string>
    <string name="friends">Friends tips</string>

    <!-- Mental tips title -->
    <string name="mental_tip_title_current_time_0">Changes</string>
    <string name="mental_tip_title_current_time_1">Calmness</string>
    <string name="mental_tip_title_current_time_2">Acceptance</string>
    <string name="mental_tip_title_current_time_3">Control</string>
    <string name="mental_tip_title_current_time_4">Mistakes</string>
    <string name="mental_tip_title_current_time_5">Panic</string>

    <string name="mental_tip_title_youself_0">Sleep</string>
    <string name="mental_tip_title_youself_1">Negative</string>
    <string name="mental_tip_title_youself_2">Monotonous days</string>
    <string name="mental_tip_title_youself_3">Loneliness</string>
    <string name="mental_tip_title_youself_4">Sport</string>

    <string name="mental_tip_title_family_0">Communication</string>
    <string name="mental_tip_title_family_1">Boundaries</string>
    <string name="mental_tip_title_family_2">Reconciliation</string>
    <string name="mental_tip_title_family_3">Concern</string>

    <string name="mental_tip_title_relationship_0">Reciprocity</string>
    <string name="mental_tip_title_relationship_1">Equality</string>
    <string name="mental_tip_title_relationship_2">Self-sufficient</string>
    <string name="mental_tip_title_relationship_3">Support</string>
    <string name="mental_tip_title_relationship_4">Harmony</string>
    <string name="mental_tip_title_relationship_5">Healthy relationship</string>

    <string name="mental_tip_title_friends_0">Duality</string>
    <string name="mental_tip_title_friends_1">Honest</string>
    <string name="mental_tip_title_friends_2">Respect</string>
    <string name="mental_tip_title_friends_3">Treasure</string>

    <!-- Mental tips desc -->
    <string name="mental_tip_current_time_0">" When events happen that destroy the conditional norm, it is impossible not to think about them, questions arise that have no answers. Also, the set of needs and habits changes, the attitude to money, free time and everything else - this is normal."</string>
    <string name="mental_tip_current_time_1">"Some people are inclined to some point of view, just to calm down. For example, they are waiting for everything to end sooner in any way — not because they wish evil to someone, but so that they can return to the previous regime. Some people may have frightening thoughts outside of their conscious desire.  "</string>
    <string name="mental_tip_current_time_2">"At this time, it is important to recognize that now everything is not the way we are used to, which means that we cannot expect the same behavior from ourselves and others. If we accept the fact that changes are taking place, we may be able to decide what to do next. "</string>
    <string name="mental_tip_current_time_3">Here we must admit that not everything is under our control: there are things that we cannot control.It is better to focus on what we can control, while it is important not to be too strict with ourselves. That is, to understand your condition and sometimes allow yourself to forget or lose something, even let some things go on without our participation.</string>
    <string name="mental_tip_current_time_4">"Anxiety depletes the resources needed for the effective operation of memory, and leads to the fact that a person overly concentrates on mistakes.When we allow ourselves to make mistakes and observe our feelings, we can study our reaction and draw conclusions. Including understanding that mistakes don't automatically make us bad.   "</string>
    <string name="mental_tip_current_time_5">"In difficult times, panic attacks, severe fear, even panic attacks appear or increase.You need to allow yourself to live the panic without doing anything with it, just watching.You can't die from a panic attack, it doesn't cause physical harm. However, you can start to be afraid of the panic itself, which will only worsen the situation "</string>

    <string name="mental_tip_youself_0">"Sleep is the most important factor affecting a person's vital activity. Without it, no one can not only feel good, but also think soberly. Therefore, try to get enough sleep and start solving difficult tasks only when you are rested.   "</string>
    <string name="mental_tip_youself_1">"Do not accumulate resentments and negative emotions in yourself. It is not necessary to deliberately tighten your black stripe, revel in your suffering. Try to put it all in the past as soon as possible.  "</string>
    <string name="mental_tip_youself_2">Monotonous gray everyday life contributes to the accumulation of internal fatigue and the emergence of depression. Bring variety to your life: meet friends, go to the theater, cinema, concerts and exhibitions</string>
    <string name="mental_tip_youself_3">Be alone. It has been proven that most people feel better after 20–30 minutes of solitude. It is important to give yourself the opportunity to be quiet for a while and be alone, just relax.</string>
    <string name="mental_tip_youself_4">"Do physical exercises. When you do sports, not only a lot of good things happen in your body at the physical level, but also substances that affect mood are produced. Endorphins are a great thing! Fall for this source of pleasure at least sometimes.    "</string>

    <string name="mental_tip_family_0">"If we consider communication with the family from the point of view of psychology, then we can talk about how important it is for children. If this is a healthy relationship, then everyone needs it, because it improves mood, gives support, etc. Nevertheless, with unhealthy relationships and the inability to establish communication, it is better to really give up this connection.  "</string>
    <string name="mental_tip_family_1">"Learn to protect your personal boundaries and respect others'. Do not let your relatives influence your life, attitude or emotional state. It is necessary to learn how to defend your position, say no and protect your interests. At the same time, it is important to do this so as not to offend another person.  "</string>
    <string name="mental_tip_family_2">"Do not run away from a conflict situation, but resolve it. Sometimes the best idea may seem to be an instant interruption of communication. First, you should try to understand the conflict, otherwise you will not be able to build effective communication further.  "</string>
    <string name="mental_tip_family_3">Be polite and be interested in the lives of your loved ones. Due to the modern rhythm of life, sometimes there is not enough time for communication and meetings with relatives. It is important to always take a minute to find out how your loved ones are doing.</string>

    <string name="mental_tip_relationship_0">"Mutual feelings and sympathy. The attitude from the past that it will be tolerated-it will be loved will not help to create resource relationships. Rather, it will be the opposite — the forces will be spent on maintaining such a relationship, and the result will be unsatisfactory. "</string>
    <string name="mental_tip_relationship_1">The emphasis on a patriarchal or matriarchal system of relations is no longer effective. The separation of people by gender builds fences between people. Equality of men and women, mutual respect, refusal to switch to personalities — that\'s what\'s important.</string>
    <string name="mental_tip_relationship_2">"A person must remain self-sufficient. You should not lose yourself in a relationship and lose yourself as a person and an expert in your business. On the contrary, it is important to learn how to use the emotional uplift from communicating with each other to develop yourself and your skills in any issue.  "</string>
    <string name="mental_tip_relationship_3">In any matters, it is important to be fans of each other — to support the partner and, if possible, help him move on. The absence of such emotions suggests that these relationships are likely to last for a short time.</string>
    <string name="mental_tip_relationship_4">Manipulative relationships lack harmony. They lead to conflicts within the family and to abuse, and ultimately give nothing but pain and frustration.</string>
    <string name="mental_tip_relationship_5">In a healthy relationship, there is no place for self-affirmation at someone else\'s expense. Determine who you are — a tyrant or a victim, and work out your behavior with a therapist.</string>

    <string name="mental_tip_friends_0">"We grow thanks to our good and bad life experiences. And we are grateful when in difficult moments of our life there is someone who is ready to support us.It is not always easy to cope with difficult life moments that arise in relationships between friends. However, if you are able to go through these trials, your friendship will become stronger and deeper. Don't give up on your friends and their support!  "</string>
    <string name="mental_tip_friends_1">"Being honest to the end is one of the hardest parts of the process called friendship. People do not always want to hear the truth about themselves or their actions. But this is exactly what you should expect from a real friend.It is necessary to call a spade a spade – even if it is difficult. Because it is not so important how exactly your friend will react at the moment – but if he is a real friend, then such a person should appreciate the fact that you are honest with him    "</string>
    <string name="mental_tip_friends_2">"There is no doubt that the best relationships are built on mutual interest. However, being a good friend means respecting the boundary where your mutual interests end. To maintain friendly relations, it is necessary to learn to recognize this boundary in time. "</string>
    <string name="mental_tip_friends_3">"It doesn't matter how long you've been friends. It also doesn't matter how strong you think your friendship is. You should never take such a relationship for granted, which you got absolutely for nothing. Do not allow yourself to underestimate friendship, because it is a real value and your wealth that should be cherished.  "</string>

    <!-- Helplines names -->
    <string name="helpline_rus_0">Moscow Psychological emergency phone</string>
    <string name="helpline_rus_1">Psychological Assistance EMERCOM of Russia</string>
    <string name="helpline_rus_2">YouAreNotAlone Women\'s Helpline</string>
    <string name="helpline_rus_3">NotHotline Man\'s Helpline</string>
    <string name="helpline_rus_4">Children\'s helpline</string>
    <string name="helpline_rus_5">Your Territory</string>

    <string name="helpline_usa_0">988 Suicide &amp; Crisis Lifeline</string>
    <string name="helpline_usa_1">Crisis Text Line</string>
    <string name="helpline_usa_2">Love is Respect</string>
    <string name="helpline_usa_3">TrevorLifeline</string>
    <string name="helpline_usa_4">StrongHearts Native Helpline</string>
    <string name="helpline_usa_5">National Problem Gambling Helpline</string>
    <string name="helpline_usa_6">Alzheimer\'s Association Helpline</string>
    <string name="helpline_usa_7">American Cancer Society</string>
    <string name="helpline_usa_8">The International Helpline</string>

    <string name="helpline_ita_0">Telefono Azzurro</string>
    <string name="helpline_ita_1">Telefono Amico Italia</string>
    <string name="helpline_ita_2">Telefono Amico Cevita</string>
    <string name="helpline_ita_3">Anti Violence And Stalking Number</string>

    <string name="helpline_fra_0">SOS Amitie</string>
    <string name="helpline_fra_1">3114, Suicide Prevention Number</string>
    <string name="helpline_fra_2">Croix-Rouge ecoute</string>
    <string name="helpline_fra_3">Solidarite Femmes</string>
    <string name="helpline_fra_4">Allô Enfance en Danger</string>
    <string name="helpline_fra_5">SOS Joueurs</string>

    <string name="helpline_chn_0">Lifeline</string>
    <string name="helpline_chn_1">Hope Line</string>
    <string name="helpline_chn_2">Jinzhou Psychological Assistance Hotline</string>

    <!-- Helplines descriptions -->
    <string name="helpline_desc_rus_0">Professional assistance in finding a solution to a problem situation: conflicts; difficulties in child-parent and marital relations; the problem of loss of the meaning of life, the experience of grief, anxiety, loss, fear, loneliness; problems of personal growth and professional activity. \nPsychologists of the emergency psychological help line provide qualified free support 24/7. Free. Confidential.</string>
    <string name="helpline_desc_rus_1">Psychologists of the Ministry of Emergency Situations of Russia provide round-the-clock telephone and Internet consultations for the population, focused on the entire spectrum of psychological problems, among which appeals regarding acute crisis states and situations are of priority importance.\nAlso on the website of the Internet service, you can go to the \"question to the psychologist\" section and remotely receive qualified psychological assistance from specialists.</string>
    <string name="helpline_desc_rus_2">This is a free and anonymous psychological support phone. Calls will be answered by professional psychologists.\nA hotline has been launched for women who feel lonely or need help - but can\'t get it. For example, if a woman is experiencing a panic attack, anxiety, or does not know how to get out of an abusive relationship.\nWe work from 9:00 to 21:00 Moscow time.</string>
    <string name="helpline_desc_rus_3">Men are more likely to be depressed and addicted in situations where the gender role implies greater control and the need to solve problems.\nMen don\'t have to go through a crisis alone.\nOur help is free and confidential, your call is answered by a professional psychologist, he helps you cope with emotions and develop a plan of action.\nAt your request, the psychologist can refer you to a face-to-face psychological counseling service.</string>
    <string name="helpline_desc_rus_4">We have experienced psychologists who are ready to help you solve those problems in your life that you cannot cope with on your own.\nTalking to an experienced professional can help: overcome bad mood and sadness, understand relationships with parents, classmates or teachers, better understand your feelings and desires, discuss personal problems that you do not want to share with loved ones.\nThe call is anonymous, free and confidential.</string>
    <string name="helpline_desc_rus_5">We are online consultants of a psychological help service for adolescents and young people (up to 23 years old).\nOn our website, you can ask for help and, while corresponding with a consultant, talk openly about the situation that worries you, about what you really feel and experience now.\nIf you need help right now, call the 24–hour all–Russian helpline 8–800–2000–122.</string>

    <string name="helpline_desc_usa_0">Our free support is provided for all mental health issues, whether you\'re in crisis or just need someone to talk to. You can contact us about anything that you\'re going through.\nWe can all help prevent suicide. The Lifeline provides 24/7, free and confidential support for people in distress, prevention and crisis resources for you or your loved ones, and best practices for professionals in the United States.\nWe\'re committed to improving crisis services and advancing suicide prevention by empowering individuals, advancing professional best practices, and building awareness.</string>
    <string name="helpline_desc_usa_1">Crisis Text Line is here to help you, whatever you\'re going through.\nFree 24/7 support at your fingertips by text message (text HOME to 741–741), online chat and WhatsApp (+1–443–787–7678).\nWe are available to talk with you about any kind of experience relating to mental health, including anxiety, depression, self-harm, stress, and thoughts of suicide.\nWe are dedicated to preventing suicide. If you are contemplating suicide or want to kill yourself, we will listen without judgment and support you.</string>
    <string name="helpline_desc_usa_2">Love is Respect offers 24/7, free and confidential support by phone, text message (text LOVEIS to 22522) and online chat. We are here for everyone, the LGBTQ+ community, parents in United States who may be looking for support with abuse &amp; domestic violence, relationships.\nWhen you contact us you will talk with one of our trained volunteers who are experienced in how to help people in your situation.</string>
    <string name="helpline_desc_usa_3">We support youth, the LGBTQ+ community in United States who may be experiencing emotional distress related to gender &amp; sexual identity, loneliness, relationships, suicide, supporting a friend or family member.</string>
    <string name="helpline_desc_usa_4">StrongHearts Native Helpline is a 24/7 safe, confidential and anonymous domestic and sexual violence helpline for Native Americans and Alaska Natives, offering culturally-appropriate support and advocacy.</string>
    <string name="helpline_desc_usa_5">National Problem Gambling Helpline offers 24/7, free and confidential support by phone, text message (SMS) and online chat. We are here for everyone in United States who may be looking for support with gambling.\nWhen you reach out to us you will talk with one of our trained counselors who will listen to you with empathy and understanding, and work together with you to find a meaningful way forward. They are experienced in knowing how to help people who have challenges like what you are going through.</string>
    <string name="helpline_desc_usa_6">The Alzheimer’s Association 24/7 Helpline is available around the clock, 365 days a year. Through this free service, specialists and master’s-level clinicians offer confidential support and information to people living with dementia, caregivers, families and the public.</string>
    <string name="helpline_desc_usa_7">We’re here 24 hours a day, 7 days a week, to help guide you through your cancer experience.\nWhether you’ve recently been diagnosed, are currently going through treatment, or are caring for a loved one with cancer, we’re here with information, day-to-day help, and emotional support every step of the way.\nWhether it’s the middle of the afternoon or the middle of the night, our cancer information specialists are here to help. Have questions about treatment options or potential side effects? We have you covered. Need a ride to chemo or a place to stay when treatment is far away? We can help. Even if you just need a friendly ear, we’re here to help and can assist in more than 200 languages (via a language line)</string>
    <string name="helpline_desc_usa_8">The International Helpline is staffed by trained phone consultants who answer the phone 24/7.  The helpline serves as a confidential safe place for you to call and talk with someone who is ready to listen to your story.  \nWhether your experience of trauma occurred last week or 50 years ago, we realize that having someone to talk with in a safe place is a first step to healing.\nWhat We Do:\nA trained phone consultant will talk with you to assess your needs.  In addition to the support you will receive on the phone, our consultants can get you connected with community resources and facilitators to help heal trauma. \nIf you are experiencing any of these symptoms, we can help.</string>

    <string name="helpline_desc_ita_0">Telefono Azzurro provides 24/7, free, compassionate and confidential support by phone and online chat.\nWe support youth in Italy who may require support with abuse &amp; domestic violence, anxiety, bullying, depression, eating &amp; body image, family issues, gambling, gender &amp; sexual identity, grief &amp; loss, loneliness, parenting, pregnancy &amp; abortion, relationships, school or work issues, self-harm, stress, substance use, suicide, supporting a friend or family member, physical illness, trauma &amp; PTSD.</string>
    <string name="helpline_desc_ita_1">"Telefono Amico Italia gives anyone the opportunity to express their suffering anonymously and confidentially, allowing each individual to recover their history and meaning within society.\nOpenness and confidentiality are guaranteed, safeguarding anonymity.   "</string>
    <string name="helpline_desc_ita_2">Helpline provided 100% by volunteers.\nWe answer the phone in a completely voluntary way, to be with you at a particular moment. We don\'t want to teach you anything, but we will listen to what you have to say by offering you a space for reflection.\nCall us, you will find a volunteer ready to listen to you, without judgment, presumption or haste.\nAlways, even for you.</string>
    <string name="helpline_desc_ita_3">We offers 24/7, free and confidential support and information by phone and online chat. We are here to help women, men in Italy who may be experiencing emotional distress related to abuse &amp; domestic violence, relationships, sexual abuse, trauma &amp; PTSD.\nWhen you reach out to us you will talk with one our friendly and supportive counselors who will collaborate with you to find solutions while giving you an empathetic and compassionate ear. They have expertise and understanding in how to help people going through difficulties similar to what you are.\nWe are always open.</string>

    <string name="helpline_desc_fra_0">S.O.S Amitié is a listening support service. On phone, as well as in chat and messaging, its volunteer listeners welcome the words of anyone who is going through a difficult period and who feels the need to be heard and listened to in their suffering.\nS.O.S Friendship listening is free, unconditional and without judgment or advice. It offers each caller the opportunity to put their suffering into words. \nIt aims to relieve anxiety, helps to take a step back, to regain confidence in one\'s own resources and to rediscover, for some, the simple taste of living.</string>
    <string name="helpline_desc_fra_1">If you are in distress and/or have suicidal thoughts, if you want to help someone in pain, you can contact to us.\n3114 is accessible 24 hours a day, 7 days a week, free of charge, throughout France.\nA care professional, specifically trained in suicide prevention, will listen to you.\nOn our website, you will find resources to better understand the suicidal crisis and advice on how to overcome it.\nThe 3114 is piloted by the Ministry of Health and Prevention.</string>
    <string name="helpline_desc_fra_2">Croix-Rouge écoute is a helpline that provides psychological support over the phone. \nThis free, anonymous number has enabled anyone in difficulty to be listened to without judgement, to discuss one\'s concerns and sometimes to find answers. \nIt is aimed at everyone, especially people who are isolated, in social, psychological, relational or material difficulty, or who are excluded from social relations and medical-psychological care.</string>
    <string name="helpline_desc_fra_3">The Fédération Nationale Solidarité Femmes is a network of 78 associations that throughout France welcome, support and house women victims of violence and their children.\nDomestic violence is a real social scourge and a serious public health problem.\nDomestic violence also affects children, who are always direct or indirect victims, and therefore society as a whole.\nThe listening service is available 24 hours a day, 7 days a week!\nA team of professional listeners ensures a benevolent listening by establishing a climate of trust that allows the person to talk about the situation and clarify their analysis of it.</string>
    <string name="helpline_desc_fra_4">We help children who find themselves in a situation of risk and danger to themselves or another child they know.\nWe also help adults who are concerned about a child who is in danger or at risk of becoming one: close relatives, extended relatives, neighbors, the educational community.\nThe danger issues that the 119 listeners face on a daily basis are varied: most of the calls concern violence against children (psychological, physical and sexual abuse), especially in the family or in an institution.</string>
    <string name="helpline_desc_fra_5">Gambling, video games, online games… can be a source of addiction for some players.\nAt this stage, the pleasure and conviviality brought about by these games no longer exist. Need, aggression, irritability, loss of control take precedence over fun.\nSOS Joueurs helps gamblers addicted to gambling, online gambling and video games.</string>

    <string name="helpline_desc_chn_0">Lifeline offers free, confidential, and anonymous support services from 10 AM – 10 PM, 365 days a year.\nOur community is available to provide a safe source of support for individuals in times of emotional distress or crisis.\nOur volunteers are available to take phone calls. However, if your call is not answered, please use our online chat function (on our website).\nIf you want to chat with us, please visit our website.</string>
    <string name="helpline_desc_chn_1">Hope 24 Hotline Volunteer Service, relying on the 24–hour crisis intervention hotline, provides the public with life education, crisis prevention, crisis intervention, stress support, supportive small groups, public lectures, crisis intervention technology promotion and training Waiting for Psychological Volunteering.\nHope Hotline 400–161–9995 was launched in Shanghai. This is a life crisis intervention hotline with volunteers who have crisis intervention expertise, volunteer management volunteers, and volunteers who provide free consultation 7*24 hours a day.</string>
    <string name="helpline_desc_chn_2">The psychological assistance hotline is a public welfare 24-hour service hotline .\nThe service purpose of the psychological assistance hotline is to strengthen the mental health services of the general public, improve the mental health level of the citizens, and prevent and reduce the occurrence of mental diseases.\nMain service scope: emotional support, psychological problem consultation, mental health knowledge popularization, psychological crisis intervention and other services.</string>

</resources>